garnethill.com 2019-02-28

# Customer Service | Your Privacy Rights | Garnet Hill

Last Updated: April 9, 2018

Garnet Hill, Inc. ("Garnet Hill") respects your privacy. As a member of the Direct Marketing Association (DMA), Garnet Hill follows the DMA privacy guidelines. The DMA's Mail Preference Service reduces the availability of your name and address to many other direct marketing companies. To learn more, click on [www.dmachoice.org](https://www.dmachoice.org/).

Garnet Hill is part of the HSN, Inc. ("HSNi") family of businesses. HSNi is a retailing powerhouse that spans the full retail spectrum including television (HSN TV and HSN2), catalogues (Cornerstone Brands), ecommerce (HSN.com and catalogue websites), and brick & mortar retail (Frontgate and Ballard Designs). For a complete list of all of HSNi's businesses, please visit [www.hsni.com](https://www.hsni.com/).

At HSNi, we respect the privacy of our customers and the importance of the information they entrust to us. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who uses one or more of our websites, views our television programming, uses our mobile applications, places orders by phone, uses our other services, or who otherwise provides us with information through various means ("Services"), the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. We summarize below the basic information policies and practices in place for all HSNi Services. To read the entire Privacy Policy of Garnet Hill, please click here. We encourage you to read the Garnet Hill Privacy Policy carefully when using our Services or transacting business with us. By using our Services or otherwise doing business with us, you are accepting the practices described in the Garnet Hill Privacy Policy. 

(read more)  
We may collect information that can identify you ("personal information"), such as your name and e-mail address, (i) when you (or other customers) provide it to us when using our Services, or (ii) from other HSNi businesses, from our business partners, or from other third parties. We may combine the personal information that we receive from different sources.We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you use our online Services:  

  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us to track users' movements around our online Services and to understand trends. 
  * We may assign your computer or device one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our online Services and to personalize your online experience. 
  * We may use standard Internet tools, such as web beacons, which collect information that tracks your use of our online Services and enables us to customize our online Services and advertisements. 

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Should we ever do so, we will comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. 

(read more)  
We may allow third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements on our online Services.

  * We do not provide any personal information to these companies. 
  * These companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect information about computers and/or devices used to view or interact with their advertisements. 
  * Some of these companies may be members of the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/), which offers consumers the ability to opt out of ad targeting by all member companies.

If you post information about yourself or others, or communicate with others using our Services, please note that we cannot control who reads your postings or what they do with the information you provide. We encourage you to use caution in posting personal information. 

(read more)  
We may use information to

  * Fulfill your requests for products and services; 
  * Offer products and services that may be of interest to you; 
  * Customize the advertising and content that you see on our Services; 
  * Facilitate use of our Services; 
  * Manage your account and your preferences; 
  * Analyze use of and improve our Services, products, and other services; 
  * Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our Services;  
and 
  * Enforce our [Conditions of Use.](https://www.garnethill.com/conditions-of-use/content)

(read more)  
We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with: 

  * Service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf; 
  * Other HSNi businesses;
  * Other businesses with which we partner or which we carefully select to offer you products, services, and promotions through our Services;  
and 
  * Other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our customers. 

We may share aggregated, non-personal information in any of the above situations and also with advertisers and others.

(read more)  
You may choose

  * Not to provide personal information, although that may result in your inability to obtain certain services or use certain features of our Services; 
  * To stop receiving promotional e-mails or newsletters from us by modifying your e-mail subscription settings here; 
  * To delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings, although if you do so, some of the features or services of our online Services may not function properly;
  * To review and update your personal information by contacting us at the e-mail address below or, if you have an online account for our Services, by logging into that account.
  * To learn about additional choices, click here

(read more)  
We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and Services. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the e-mail address you most recently provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our online Services.

If you have any questions about this summary, the Garnet Hill Privacy Policy, or our information practices, please contact us by e-mail or postal mail below: 

Toll Free: 800.870.3513  
Email: [customerservice@garnethill.com](mailto:customerservice@garnethill.com?subject=Privacy%20Information)  
Mail: Garnet Hill  
Attn: Customer Service  
231 Main Street  
Franconia, NH 03580

Currently, our online Services do not recognize automated browser signals regarding "do not track" instructions. If we develop this capability in the future, we will describe how we do so in the Garnet Hill Privacy Policy. Please note that third parties may collect personal information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our online Services or browse other websites. For more information about "Do Not Track," please visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](https://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

© 2007 - 2015 HSN, Inc. All rights reserved.

## Linked Information

 **Cookies:**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer or device for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our online Services. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive or device for an extended period of time.   
We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our online Services to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our Services, content, and advertising. You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our online Services may not function properly. We may allow third parties, including HSNi companies, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our Services. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our Services do not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer or device, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third party's privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/ "opens new window") ). 

**Web Beacons:**  
Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags, or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user's computer hard drive or device, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in e-mail) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.   
Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages, and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our online Services from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website. 

**Mobile Services:**  
We may also collect non-personal information from your mobile device if you have downloaded any of our mobile application(s). This information is generally used to help us deliver the most relevant information to you. Examples of information that may be collected and used may include, but are not limited to, your geographic location, how you use our application(s), and information about the type of device you use. This information is sent to us as aggregate information, and is not traceable back to any individual and cannot be used to identify an individual. To opt out of sharing this information, such as location, please review the terms and conditions before you download the application, or you may review the settings on your mobile device or you may choose at any time to uninstall our application(s) from your mobile device.
